[{"id": 2966, "question": "With around 40,000 students, the Politecnico di Milano is the largest and most technical university in Italy, offering undergraduate, graduate and other courses in engineering, architecture and design. Founded in 1863, just two years after Italy was united, Milan Polytechnic is international famous. Many of its graduates now work in big companies abroad like M.I.T., Caltech and Oxbridge. Yet the Politechnic has a problem. As you know, here in Italy people speak Italian. Beautiful though the language may be, it is not a good choice for engineers when they're building a way in Norway or designing a bridge in Vietnam. For better or worse, the global tongue of engineers is English. Hoping to attract more international students, the Politechnic decided to run its doctor's courses in English onl...\n\nQ: The main idea of the passage is that the Politechnic decision to run its doctor's courses in English only   _  .", "options": ["attracts more international students", "sends more students to work abroad", "makes some teachers out of work", "meets with different responses"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3291, "question": "Bicycles are a great way to get around. They're fun to ride, especially down hills. And, as you speed along the road, you might also think of ways in which you could improve your bike-- make it safer, more efficient, or more comfortable. In fact, the two-wheeled machines make for some cool science projects. This year's Intel International Science and Engineering Fair (ISEF), held last May in Cleveland, featured(had)three bicycle projects from three countries. Like many of the other experiments presented at ISEF, the bike projects showed that some of the most interesting scientific research often begins by taking a closer look at things you care about. Renato Angulo Chu had even grander ambitions. The 12th-grader from Lima, Peru, wanted to _ some of his country's economic troubles. \"I see a...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["ISEF is an exhibiton displaying bicycle experiments designed by students.", "Looking closely at things you are concerned about can lead to scientific research.", "Renato's improvement of the bicycle has solved the country's great problem.", "Renato's special bicycle will soon be put into use in remote areas.'"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 242, "question": "As many people hit middle age, they often start to notice that their memory and mental attention are not what they used to be. We suddenly can't remember where we put the keys just a moment ago, or an old friend's name, or the name of an old band we used to love. It happens to most of us, but is it unavoidable? Scientists are increasingly showing that there's actually a lot that can be done. It turns that the brain needs exercise in much the same way as our muscles do, and the right mental workouts can improve our basic cognitive functions. Now, a new San Francisco Web-based company has taken it a step further and developed the first \"brain training program\" designed to actually help people improve and regain their mental sharpness. Called Lumosity, it was designed by some of the leading e...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of Lumosity?", "options": ["To exercise the brain and muscles.", "To combine exercises with a web-based program.", "To improve basic cognitive functions.", "To improve students' scores on test."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1622, "question": "Your children's teacher will be providing extra time for test preparation. This school year's test will be held on January 8 and 9. The test preparation time is open to all students, and we strongly encourage your children to attend. This year we are changing the time for our test preparation: it will be on Thursday mornings from 8:10 to 8:50. This helps children who ride the bus and cannot stay for the after-school period. It also helps avoid conflicts with after-school activities. Danielle and Marina will be working with the recent new test takers 6 days on the following Thursdays: 15th, Nov; 29th, Nov; 6th, Dec; 13th, Dec.; 20th, Dec. and 3rd, Jan. Besides the test preparation lectures on these dates, teachers are already putting test preparation into their usual courses. We are finding...\n\nQ: Why did the school encourage all the students to take part in the test preparation?", "options": ["Test preparation is what they always do.", "The students will learn what will be included in the final exam.", "Test preparation helps students to be more interested in reading and confident.", "The test is a long way off and there are better things to do."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2051, "question": "It was just three degrees above zero. \"That's cold,\" thought Jane as she got ready to deliver her morning papers. Jane has 50 customers, and on cold mornings when she couldn't ride her bike, it took her more than an hour to make her rounds. As she collected her papers and put them into a big canvas bag, Jane regretted that she hadn't finished her math homework the night before. There was still time. She'd hurry with the papers and finish the math before breakfast. Less than an hour later, Jane was nearly finished. She had only five customers to go. She could then head for home to complete her math while her mom fixed breakfast. As she rounded the corner, she saw a car in the middle of the street. It was Mr. Zimmerman, the elderly man who walked with a walking stick. His car was out of gas....\n\nQ: The reading doesn't say but we can infer that  _", "options": ["Jane bought the gas for Mr. Zimmerman", "usually Jane delivers papers by bike", "Mr. Robert doesn't like Jane at school", "Mr. Zimmerman had to leave the car for Jane"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1465, "question": "I have only once been in trouble with the law.The whole process of being arrested and taken to court was a rather unpleasant experience at the time, but it makes a good story now. What makes it rather disturbing was the arbitrary circumstances both of my arrest and my subsequent fate in court. It happened in February about twelve years ago.I had left school a couple of months before that and was not due to go to university until the following October.I was still living at home at the time. One morning I was in Richmond, a suburb of London near where I lived.I was looking for a temporary job so that I could save up some money to go traveling.As it was a fine day and I was in no hurry, I was taking my time, looking in shop windows, strolling in the park, and sometimes just stopping and looki...\n\nQ: In the opinion of one of the policeman who had arrested the author, the whole thing might not have occurred if   _  .", "options": ["he had protested strongly at the time", "he had begged to be allowed to go home", "he hadn't wandered aimlessly", "he had tried to look cool"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2150, "question": "With thousands of waterfalls across the world, it is difficult to choose the best but the following list contains some of the world's most amazing and beautiful ones! Iguazu Falls-The Iguazu Falls is located on the border of Brazil and Argentina and it is well-known for its scenic beauty. Though it is just about 89 meters high, it ranks as the fourth best waterfall in the world because of its beauty. The U-shaped cliff in the waterfall which is known as the Devil's throat is the most striking feature of the waterfall. Angel Falls-The Angel Falls, named after its discoverer James Crawford Angel, is the world's highest waterfalls, falling from a height of 979 meters. It is located in the Bolivar state in Venezuela. A unique feature of the falls is that most of the water falling down gets blo...\n\nQ: From the text we know that the highest waterfalls in the world is  _  .", "options": ["Iguazu Falls", "Angel Falls", "Niagara Falls", "Rhine Falls"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1957, "question": "In today's throw away society, dealing with the city's growing mountain of waste is an inereasing challenge for the city countil . Recently. Edinburgh is faced with the problem of dssposing of about250,000 Million tons of waster a year . Despite different ways to dispose of much of it in a green manner---largely through encouraging tecycling---its aging facilities such as the Powderhall landfill do not have the ability to deal with it. The European Union(EU) has issued a new policy, regulating how such mountains of waster are to hr disposed of. The five councils (Edinburgh. East Lothian. West Lothian. Midlethian and Borders) face fine around $18million a year from 2013 it they don't inerease recycling levels and rely less on landfill. With this in mind, the coumlls got together with the id...\n\nQ: The five councils worked out a plan to build an incinerator plant to_.", "options": ["reduce the roast of burying waste", "meets the EU requirements", "speed up waste recycling", "tempter landfill sites"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 402, "question": "prefix = st1 /PITTSBURGH, Sept. 7 -- At 26, many people haven't even decided on a career. Luke Ravenstahl, cashing in on his family's political tradition, is already the mayor of Pittsburgh, the youngest mayor of any major city in the country. Although mayors elsewhere have been younger, Jeff Dunkel was 18 in 2001 when he was elected mayor of Mount Carbon, small towns inNew York, and elsewhere have also elected teenagers as mayors. But,Tallahassee, is the only other city with a population over 100,000 that has had a mayor as young as Mr. Ravenstahl. A supporter of Mr. Ravenstahl said concerns about Mr. Ravenstahl's age would _ once the city saw his work ethic. But now comes the hard part. As he strives to be taken seriously and take charge of a city only recently back from the brink of ban...\n\nQ: Where can you find this article?", "options": ["A magazine", "A brochure about politicians", "A newspaper", "An advertisement about some mayor candidates"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 321, "question": "Cutting global warming pollution would not only make the planet healthier, it would make people healthier too, new research suggested. Cutting carbon dioxide emissions could save millions of lives, mostly by reducing preventable deaths from heart and lung diseases, according to studies released Wednesday and published in a special issue of The Lancet, a British medical journal. \"Relying on fossil fuels leads to unhealthy lifestyles, increasing our chances of getting sick and in some cases takes years from our lives,\" US Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius said in a telecast briefing from her home state of Kansas. \"As greenhouse gas emissions go down, so do deaths from cardiovascular and respiratory diseases. This is not a small effect.\" Instead of looking at the health il...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["London and Delhi have already benefited from reducing greenhouse gas emissions", "switching to low-polluting cars would save 160 lives in London each year", "walking and biking instead of driving will reduce the chance of heart disease", "attacking health problems and dealing with climate change are contradictory"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 306, "question": "Israel has passed a law banning the use of underweight models in advertising. Known as the \"Photoshop Law\", it also requires that agencies tell their audience if they've digitally changed pictures to make models look thinner. The new law forbids the use of models with a body mass index of 18.5 or less, a standard based on internationally accepted measures. The figure matches the set of fixed limits by the U. S. Department of Health. The law doesn't set a money amount that can be gained in court from such a _ . Lawmakers realize that it may be a long and difficult process to prove in court that a company broke the new law, but they feel that simply having the law in place will accomplish what they want; stopping advertising companies from continuing to influence Israelis with images of unhe...\n\nQ: What can we know from the passage?", "options": ["All models are happy about the law.", "All advertising agencies are happy about the law.", "The law makes no sense.", "There are arguments over the beauty standard of models."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1645, "question": "An old friend from California called from the airport to tell me that he had arrived. I was not able to leave the office, but I had made plans for his arrival. After explaining where my new house was, I told him that I had left the key under the doormat . Since I knew it would be pretty late before I could get home, I suggested that he make himself at home and help himself to anything that was in the refrigerator . Two hours later my friend phoned me from the house. At the moment, he said, he was listening to some of my records after having had a delicious meal. Now, he said, he was drinking a glass of orange juice. When I asked him if he had had any difficulty finding the house, he answered that the only problem was that he had not been able to find the key under the doormat, but luckily,...\n\nQ: An old friend of mine called   _  .", "options": ["to tell me to meet him at the airport", "to tell me about his arrival", "to ask me to leave the office", "to ask me to make plans for his arrival"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3372, "question": "Farmer John and Farmer Bob were neighbors. For more than 30 years, they had been getting along very well. Then their good relationship broke. It began with a small thing, then bitter words, and then weeks of silence. One morning Farmer John woke up to find a stream between the two farms. \"It must be Bob,\" John thought. Then one day there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a carpenter standing at the doorway. \"I'm looking for a few days' work,\" the carpenter said. \"I do have a job for you,\" John said. \"Look across the stream at that farm. That's my neighbor Bob. He dug a stream between the two farms. I want you to build a fence--an 8-foot fence. I don't want to see his place or his face any more. I don't have such a neighbor!\" The carpenter said, \"I think I know what to do, si...\n\nQ: Farmer John asked the carpenter to build a fence because  _  .", "options": ["he wanted to protect his farm", "he didn't want to do it himself", "he wouldn't like to see Bob", "he wanted to find him something to do"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1978, "question": "We found out that Jenny was suffering hearing loss when she was four and a half years old. Several operations and speech classes later, when she was seven, we found out that Jenny had Juvenile Rheumatoid Arthritis . She could not put pressure on the heels of her feet, so she walked on tiptoe , and when the pain became unbearable, I carried her. Jenny was fortunate, though, because she did not suffer the deformities , often associated with JRA. All through grade school, and on into high school, Jenny suffered, yet never complained. She took her medicine, and I would often wrap her feet in steaming towels, and hold her until the pain eased. But, as soon as she could stand the pain, Jenny, immediately, carried on, as though she were pain-free. She wore a smile on her face, a song on her lips,...\n\nQ: The passage is probably written by  _  .", "options": ["Jenny's parent", "Jenny's football coach", "a doctor", "a reporter"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2727, "question": "Two people have died after two separate university shootings in Texas and Arizona, just hours apart. One person was killed and three injured in the first shooting at Northern Arizona University early on Friday. Later that morning a shooting at a student complex near Texas Southern University left one person dead. In Arizona, police named the gunman there as Steven Jones, an 18-year-old first year student at Northern Arizona University.Mr. Jones told police he was approached by a group of men and attacked. He fled, produced a gun from his pocket and opened fire when the men caught up with him, Arizona police said. Witnesses told police that the victims were unarmed. The second shooting in Texas happened later on Friday morning at the University Courtyard Apartments on the edge of the Housto...\n\nQ: Mr. Obama probably agreed that   _  .", "options": ["gun control is too strict in most parts of America, especially in universities", "designation of Umpqua community college as a gun-free zone is a wrong decision", "Americans should be united to prevent criminal shooting from happening so frequently", "A failure to treat mental health problems caused the shooting at Umpqua Community College"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3390, "question": "Little Tom down the street calls our dog \"The keep dog\".Zip is a sheep dog. But when Tom tries to say\" Seep\", it comes out \"keep\". And in a way Tom is right. Zip is always bringing things home for us to keep! I'll tell you about some of them. Zip's first present was a shoe. It was made of green silk. We didn't know how Zip found the shoe. But after a moment Mary, my big sister, told me the shoe had a strange smell. I nodded and held my nose. \"What do you think it is?\" \"It smells like something for cleaning. I think someone tried to clean a spot off the shoe. Then he put it at the door to dry.\" \"Along came Zip. And good-bye shoe!\" I said.\"We should take it back.\" \"We can't \".said my sistter. \"Maybe little Tom is right,\" Mary said. \"Maybe Zip is a keep dog!\"...\n\nQ: What made the shoe strange was   _  .", "options": ["its colour", "its smell", "its size", "that it was a silk one"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2470, "question": "Every year in the first week of English class, some students inform me that writing is too hard. They never write, unless homework requires it. They find the writing process painful and difficult. How awful it is to be able to speak in a language but not to write in it, especially with its rich vocabulary. Being able to speak but not write is like living in _ and never leaving one small room. When I meet students who think they can't write, I know, as a teacher my duty is to show them the rest of the rooms. My task is to build fluency and accuracy while providing the opportunity in any writing activity to enhance the moral and emotional development of my students. One great way to do this is by having students write in a journal in class every day. Writing ability is like strength training...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the passage?", "options": ["To encourage students to keep a journal every day.", "To analyze students' problems in learning languages.", "To stress the importance of writing in language learning.", "To introduce an effective way of improving students' writing."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2778, "question": "Hunan Satellite TV is losing its leading position? There's reason for saying this. In 2012, the reality talent show , the voice of China, on the Zhejiang Television became the most popular program in China. The reaon for its popularity was really because its excellent quality? Or can we assume that without any opponent, we can't tell a contestant is winning because he is really talented or because there's no comparison? The administrative department really contributed a lot in the popularity of the voice of China. In the past, there was no other draft shows ranked as high as Super GirlandSuper Boy. Even though there were some draft shows which seemed to share the popularity, it never turned out ture. All the other draft shows were shodowed by the ones on Hunan TV. One example was that sinc...\n\nQ: The following factors are important in making the voice of China popular EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["the unique quality of the voice of China", "the policy support from SARFT and the administrative department", "the favorable broadcasting time.", "the shortage of good opponents"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 632, "question": "In the US and Britain, the slogan around colleges was \"Save water. Shower with a friend.\" Now, Wuhan University has come up with another system for the campus bathhouse. It charges students for the amount of time in a shower. Before entering the bathhouse, students pay for the amount of time they want in the shower with cash or their student ID card. The clock starts ticking the minute the tape is turned on. It pauses when a button is pressed for soap. An integrated circuit (IC) card reader at each tap shows the time. No money, no water. The benefits of the new system can be seen with the old system, which charged 1 Yuan for each person regardless of time in the shower. The university used about 320 tons of water daily under the old system, but only 160 tons now. Many students use the new ...\n\nQ: In which column can you find this passage?", "options": ["Culture.", "Society.", "Campus Life.", "Lifestyle."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1674, "question": "Thanks a Million, Dad I was born disabled.A difficult birth, feet first, my head stuck.By my first birthday, I couldn't stand or walk. When I was three, the doctor told dad I had cerebral palsy .A loss of oxygen to my brain had destroyed brain signals to the right side of my body. But no son of my dad' s was going to be disabled.Every morning before breakfast and every evening before bed, my dad placed me on the bedroom floor to exercise my right leg.The muscles were shrunk and twisted together.Back and forth up and down, my dad pushed and pulled the muscles into shape. But my dad' s exercise of passion didn't stop there.For my 13th birthday, he threw me a special party.When everybody was gone, he brought me to open a large box, it was a-set of boxing gloves.We put them on.My dad kept on b...\n\nQ: What caused the author' s disability?", "options": ["A failed operation.", "The doctor's forceps.", "An accident in a game.", "Shrunken and twisted muscles."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1127, "question": "Father's Garden My father was always a good gardener. One of my earliest memories is standing without shoes in the freshly tilled soil, my hands blackened from digging in the ground. As a child, I loved following Dad around in the garden. I remember Dad pushing the tiller ahead in perfectly straight lines. Dad loved growing all sorts of things: yellow and green onions, watermelons almost as big as me, rows of yellow corn, and our favorite--- red tomatoes. As I grew into a teenager, I didn't get so excited about gardening with Dad. Instead of magical land of possibility, it had turned into some kind of prison. As Dad grew older, his love for gardening never disappeared. After all the kids were grown and had started families of their own, Dad turned to gardening like never before. Even when ...\n\nQ: Why did the author start his garden with tomatoes?", "options": ["He wanted to honor his father.", "His son liked the fields of tomatoes.", "He only knew how to grow tomatoes.", "He thought tomatoes were easy to manage."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2761, "question": "When Danny Wallace, 26, got bored, he put an ad on the worldwide web reading simply: \"Join Me. Send a passport photo.\" A year and a half later his east London flat is the headquarters for a global internet-based \"club\" whose members carry out good deeds for strangers every Friday. It's not common for people in London to talk to strangers. If you see someone struggling with something, part of the brain goes \"I want to help\". But the trained part of the brain says: \"They will think you are mad or going to mug them\", so you walk away. Join Me now has about 3,000 members around the world who do an act of kindness every Friday. For example, I'm usually out on a Friday so I go for one of the standard acts -- the unexpected cup of coffee. You might be sitting in a cafe and see an old man in the c...\n\nQ: According to the passage, members of Join Me often   _  .", "options": ["put an advertisement on the worldwide web", "go out and make friends with strangers", "do an act of kindness every Friday", "buy coffees for the strangers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3386, "question": "Life is too short to waste a moment, so while you still have time, let your hair down, remove that \"boring\" tag in your so-called life and start making it worthwhile. Below are some tips that will help you live a wonderful life. 1. Keep a Positive Attitude. Enjoy what you have and work on getting the things you desire. Psychologists believe that optimism is a good defense against unhappiness, so it is better to keep your optimism alive. Feeling sad about your life will only make you sadder, so be happy. 2. Don't Be Afraid to Take Risks. Life is all about taking risks, and that's the exciting part of it. Challenges and failure are part of life. Once you learn how to take risks, you'll soon realize how good it feels not to let moments pass you by. 3. You only have one life, so make it worthw...\n\nQ: The writer may NOT agree that   _  .", "options": ["feeling sad about your life does you no good", "it's good to keep yourself busy doing something", "you shouldn't go to a new place where you have no friends", "you should enjoy the present instead of always thinking of the past"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 579, "question": "Read the following reviews for movies that are showing at the moment. And then answer questions. Happiness(Romance) Happinesstells the story of two people (Lisa Turbot and Danny Roy) who work for different advertising companies. They talk on the phone all the time and don't like each other. But then they _ by e-mail and fall in love. This movie will be very popular with teenagers and people who like romances. It also has beautiful music. I Scream(Thriller) InI Scream, Paul (Colin Jacks) is a young man who joins a thriller club. Each of the members tries to frighten the others. Paul is told to stay in an old house for the night. Everyone who has tried to stay in the house before has died. This movie is very frightening but also quite silly. It doesn't make sense for Paul to stay in the hous...\n\nQ: A thriller is most probably a film which tells something   _  .", "options": ["instructive", "frightening", "humorous", "interesting"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 877, "question": "A new international study shows that six people die every minute from smoking. That is 3 million deaths around the world every year. If the present rate of smoking continues, the number of deaths each year from smoking could rise to 10 million by the year 2020. The study describes smoking is the biggest cause of deadly diseases among grown-ups in industrial countries. So far most of the smoking deaths have happened to men, especially in developing countries. A researcher at the World Health Organization says 70% of Chinese men smoke more than 15 cigarettes each day. In Latin America about 50% of the men are smokers. There also are a very large number of smokers in Russia and in Eastern Europe. And 25% of all smoking deaths worldwide are in those areas of the world. Scientists say smoking w...\n\nQ: If people don't stop smoking, they will   _  .", "options": ["pollute the air", "be in poor health", "become stupid", "waste a lot of money"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 286, "question": "Born in America in 1898, William was an extraordinary boy, gifted with an amazing IQ between 250 and 300. The genius went to a grammar school when he was only 6 years old and graduated just within 7 months. At the age of 11, he became the youngest student of the Harvard University. He graduated with high scores at the age of 16 and entered Harvard Law School at 18. Gifted with an amazing IQ between 220 and 230, Terence Tao makes it to this list of the people with the highest IQ in the world. Born in Adelaide, Australia in 1975, this genius first displayed his incredible intelligence at a mere age of 2, when he managed to solve basic arithmetic questions on his own. At the age of 16, he graduated with both Master's and Bachelor's degrees at the Flinders University. He has been considered as...\n\nQ: Who once worked on the project to conquer planet Mars?", "options": ["William", "Terence Tao", "Christopher Hirata", "Albert Einstein"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 63, "question": "Nelson Mandela was a figure of international fame, and many details of his life and career were public knowledge. But here are four things you may not have known about the late South African leader. 1. He was a boxing fan. In his youth, Nelson Mandela enjoyed boxing and long-distance running. Even during the 27 years he spent in prison, he would exercise every morning. \"I did not enjoy the violence of boxing so much as the science of it. I was curious by how one moved one's body to protect oneself, how one used a strategy both to attack and retreat, how one paced oneself over a match,\" he wrote in his autobiography Long Walk to Freedom. 2. His original name was not Nelson. Rolihlahla Mandela was nine years old when a teacher at the primary Methodist school where he was studying in Qunu, So...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["Nelson Mandela was not his original name.", "Nelson Mandela was the name given by his teacher.", "Nelson Mandela had been studying the law nonstop for 50 years.", "Nelson Mandela had started his own law firm before he got a law degree."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 759, "question": "Among various programs, TV talk shows have covered every inch of space on daytime television. But no two shows are more opposite in content, while at the same time standing out above the rest, than the Jerry Springer and Oprah Winfrey shows. Jerry Springer could easily be considered the king of \"rubbish talk\". The show takes the ever-common talk show titles of love, sex, cheating, and hate, to a different level. Clearly, the Jerry Springer show is about the dark side of society, yet people are willing to eat up the troubles of other people's lives. Like Jerry Springer, Oprah Winfrey takes the TV talk show to its top. But Oprah goes in the opposite direction. The show is mainly about the improvement of society and different quality of life. Contents are from teaching your children lessons, ...\n\nQ: What is the advantage of the Jerry Springer show?", "options": ["The show exposes the dark sides of society.", "The show pours poisonous waste into society.", "Jerry sums up the whole idea of the show.", "Jerry talks about the improvement of society."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3211, "question": "Every day is a gift, and if you look forward to spending each day with happiness, wake up every morning with a positive attitude and enjoy a beautiful day! Set up a daily plan for yourself and ensure that you reserve enough time for your homework. Also, don't forget to spare some time for play! Stop being lazy and start participating in your life instead of just watching it pass by. Try to do something fun and constructive every day. _ , write something interesting in your diary, try a new hobby, spend time with your friends, or just watch your favorite show on television, and you will see how every moment of your day unfolds. You'll achieve better results, and ultimately greater success. However, every day will not be the way you want it to be. Some days will be good, while some will be b...\n\nQ: Who are the intended readers of the passage?", "options": ["Teachers", "Students", "Workers", "People in general"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 26, "question": "Very soon the Rabbit noticed Alice, as she went hunting about, and called out to her, \"What are you doing out here? Run home this moment, and fetch me a pair of gloves and a fan! Quick, now!\" Alice was so much frightened that she ran off at once in the direction it pointed to. She saw a little house, on the door of which was a plate with the name \"W. RABBIT\". She went in and hurried upstairs. By this time she had found her way into a tidy little room with a table in the window, and on it a fan and two or three pairs of tiny white kid gloves: she took up the fan and a pair of the gloves, and was just going to leave the room, when her eye fell upon a little bottle that stood near the looking-glass. There was no label this time with the words' DRINK ME,' but she opened it and put it to her li...\n\nQ: Alice grew so big because she   _  .", "options": ["had special magical power", "wore the Rabbit's gloves.", "drank something in the bottle", "wanted to frighten the Rabbit"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 943, "question": "It was near dusk, and Kim Cooper and her husband, Steve, were trucking through northern Kentucky transportation auto parts from Louisville to Detroit for a goods company. \"Steve, wake up!\" she shouted. \"There's a truck on fire!\" Inside the burning truck, Ronnie Sanders, 38, was fighting for his life. He'd been running a heavy load of tractors and forklifts from Georgia to Indianapolis when a van in front of him stopped suddenly in traffic on the icy road. As Ronnie bore down, he could see children in the backseat. The truck's bulk would probably protect him from the worst of the impact, but the force of 23 tons would likely crush everyone inside the van. \"I figured instead of killing other people, I'd just put the truck in the ditch.\" At the bottom, rocks cut a fuel tank, which caught fire...\n\nQ: How did Steve put out the flames in Ronnie's legs?", "options": ["He beat the flames with Ronnie's shirt.", "He beat the flames with his own shirt.", "He put out the fire with a tank of water.", "He put out the fire with a bag of sand."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 791, "question": "In my living room, there is a plaque that advises me to \"Bloom where you are planted.\" It reminds me of Dorothy. I got to know Dorothy in the early 1980s, when I was teaching Early Childhood Development through a program with Union College in Barbourville, Kentucky. The job responsibilities requested occasional visits to the classroom of each teacher in the program. Dorothy stands out in my memory as one who \"bloomed\" in her remote area. Dorothy taught in a school In Harlan County, Kentucky, Appalachian Mountain area. To get to her school from the town of Harlan, I followed a road winding around the mountain. In the eight-mile journey, I crossed the same railroad track five times, giving the possibility of getting caught by the same train five times. Rather than feeling excited by this dri...\n\nQ: In the journey, the author was most disappointed at seeing   _  .", "options": ["the long track", "the poor houses", "the same train", "the winding road"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2454, "question": "Norway tops the list of countries that offers the best social policies for people over 60. Afghanistan is rated the worst. The rankings appear in the new Global Age Watch Index. Help Age International published the index of 96 countries that are home to 790-million people 60 and older. Chief Executive Officer Toby Porter said, \"For too long, older people have been excluded from international and national development planning. We have a world which is ageing fast. And what the index does is to compare and rank countries from best to worst countries in the world to grow old,\" he said. The Global Age Watch Index rates countries in four categories. \"Health, income, what we call capability - ability to carry on contributing employment. And then the final one about enabling environment - what do...\n\nQ: According to Toby Porter, he does not agree that  _  .", "options": ["older people have not been included in the developing plan for a long time", "it makes little sense to rank countries from best to worst in the world to grow old", "more attention should be paid to older people in a world that is ageing fast", "South Africa is doing lots of positive things to improve the older people's conditions"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1027, "question": "Home to me means a sense of familiarity and nostalgia . It's fun to come home. It looks the same. It smells the same. You'll realize what's changed is you. Home is where we ran remember pain, live, and some other experiences; We parted here; My parents met here; I won three championships here. If I close my eyes, I can still have a clear picture in mind of my first home. I walk in the door and see a brown sofa surrounding a low glass-top wooden table. To the right of the living room is my first bedroom. It's empty, but it's where my earliest memories are. There is the dining room table where I celebrated birthdays, and where I cried on Halloween-when I didn't want to wear the skirt my mother made for me. I always liked standing on that table because it made me feel tall and strong. If I si...\n\nQ: Sometimes when she feels lost, the author will   _  .", "options": ["Open the window at night", "lie down in bed to have a dream", "try to bring back a sense of home", "go to Los Angeles to visit her mom"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 996, "question": "Most painters discover a style of painting that is fit for them and stick to that, especially if people admire their pictures. But Picasso, the great Spanish painter, was like a man who had not yet found his own particular style of painting. He kept on struggling to find the perfect expression till his death in 1973. Some of Picasso's painting are rich, soft color1ed and beautiful. Others are ugly and cruel and strange. But such paintings allow us to imagine things for ourselves. They force us to say to ourselves,\"What does he see that makes him paint like that?\" And we begin to look under the surface of the things we see.. Picasso painted thousands of pictures in different styles. Sometimes he painted the natural look of things. Sometimes he seemed to break them apart and throw the pieces...\n\nQ: Why have people called Picasso \"the youngest painter in the world?\"", "options": ["Because he observed things with the eye and the mind.", "Because he looked young when he was old.", "Because he never stopped painting he was old.", "Because he never gave up looking for something new."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2302, "question": "Some diaries from Jackie Chan's blog January 4, 2009 Lately I've been busy in Beijing having meetings to discuss my new movie. I also attended John Wu's ceremony of his new movie,Red Cliff,which took two years to complete. I'm good friends with the director John Wu and the main actor Tony Leung. January 5, 2009 Today I went to record a television program for Beijing TV calledVolunteers Across China. This TV program is a large-scale reality show that is based on the idea that \"good people reap good rewards\" and it hopes to encourage people to be more aware and help the \"good people\" who are in difficult situations. January 6, 2009 I'm very pleased to _ that my Jackie Chan automobile website is set up and officially operating! I hope that through this automotive website, I can get in touch w...\n\nQ: The TV programVolunteers Across Chinatries to", "options": ["find some rich people who are able to help the poor.", "encourage people to look after the young.", "ask people to help \"good people\" who are in trouble.", "make China more and more famous all over the word."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1304, "question": "Signing up for a digital TV service provides you with access to over 200 channels from all over the globe. However, television today is dominated by adult language, making it hard for concerned families to find channels suitable for young eyes. Therefore, most movie channels are automatically removed form the list of TV channels for an entire family. The following are some good ones based on popularity on a global scale. Discovery Channel Discovery and its many channels can be considered as the founding father of informative channels on television. What National Geographic does in a scholastic manner, Discovery tries to do in an entertaining manner--educating the masses about anything and everything. Fox Family Finding a movie channel that broadcasts pictures suitable for teenagers and kid...\n\nQ: If people want to know about what a traditional family is like, they can choose   _  .", "options": ["Fox Family", "Nickelodeon", "ABC Family", "Living"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 35, "question": "Hi, everybody! Welcome to our newly-opened Richards Cinema Bookstore! Now let me introduce to you some of the new film books in our store. Are you Chinese film fans? OK, here comes the latest 25 New Takes about Chinese films. It is a collection of 25 fresh readings of different Chinese films from the 1930s to the present. In recent years, Chinese films are very popular in the States, such as Crouching Tiger and Hidden Dragon, Hero, and Flowers of Shanghai. Do you like French films? Well, here is The French Cinema Book. It covers French films from the 1890s to the beginning of the 21st century. It is written for all lovers of French cinema: students and teachers, specialists and fans, and so on. Maybe you are Indian film fans and star-chasers. Then here is Encyclopedia of Indian Cinema. The...\n\nQ: The purpose of the speaker is   _  .", "options": ["to satisfy the customers' various tastes", "to keep the authors in the cinema bookstore", "to offer the tourists chances to meet the film stars", "to turn the readers into film producers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 112, "question": "Welcome to Coteborg University Coteborg University is one of Sweden's largest and most popular universities. We are very proud of this and believe that there are several reasons for our popularity. The principal reasons we believe to be the high quality of our education and research and the broad range of courses that we offer. In addition to this, Coteborg University provides an attractive and exceptionally high-standard study environment. Most parts of the university are situated in the city centre and this enriches city life as well as student life. Coteborg has a lot to offer its students: it has a rich and varied cultural life with many theatres, concerts and festivals. For those looking for outdoor life, forests and vast recreation areas are not far away from the city centre; the sea...\n\nQ: What's the main purpose of this passage?", "options": ["To bring fame to Coteborg University.", "To introduce the wonderful cultural life in Coteborg University.", "To declare Coteborg University's goal and interest.", "To attract students all over the world to apply for Coteborg University."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1585, "question": "Zoe, Damacela, 19, didn't have nice clothes when she was young. It wasn't easy for Zoe's hard-working single mother to make ends meet. They moved in and out of homeless shelters. Everything changed for Zoe in grade nine. At that time, she heard about a sewing class at her school. She signed up and couldn't wait to turn her designs into clothes. The color of the first dress she made was white-black strips. Soon the clothes she wore were all made by her. Other girls at school loved her designs too. They asked her if they could buy dresses from her. Zoe sold her first dress for $13. Unfortunately, it cost her $25 to make the dress. \"I had the creativity in designs,\" says Zoe. \"But I really had no idea about business.\" Zoe kept selling the clothes she designed. Her business was booming, and ev...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["How Zoe learned to design clothes.", "A poor girl achieved success in business.", "How Zoe got a prize in a contest.", "A poor girl was invited to a TV show."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3204, "question": "At an airport I overheard a father and a daughter in their last moments together. They had announced her plane's departure. Standing near the door, he said to his daughter: \"I love you. I wish you enough.\" \"Daddy, our life together has been more than enough. Your love is all I ever needed. I wish you enough too, Daddy.\" They kissed goodbye and she left. He walked over toward the window where I was seated. I tried not to _ his privacy, but he welcomed me in by asking: \"Did you ever say goodbye to someone knowing it would be forever?\" \"Yes, I have,\" I replied. \"Forgive me for asking, but why is this a forever goodbye?\" I asked. \"I am old and she lives much too far away. I have challenges ahead and the reality is that her next trip back will be for my funeral. \" \"When you were saying goodbye ...\n\nQ: From the passage we know that  _  .", "options": ["the young man is a writer", "the talk between the two men is common", "the daughter lives far away from her daddy", "the young man is interested in the old man"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2671, "question": "\"Wake up. Alicia is waiting for you outside,\" my mother called from the kitchen. My mother didn't like me going for this weekend to my friend's house in the mountains. \"I trust you, but I don't trust the people out there,\" she said seriously. \"I'm going to be fine,\" were my last words before closing the door of the Jeep. The vehicle went along the dusty road and my mother grew smaller in the distance. The trip over the rough road was uncomfortable. It was scary to climb the steep hills surrounded by great pines. After a long trip we finally arrived at the house. From the moment I got there I knew I would forever love the house. It was decorated like an old country home. My room was small, yet set up nicely. That night I went to sleep early, not because I didn't want to continue my search, ...\n\nQ: How did the author find the trip to her friend's house?", "options": ["Interesting and impressive.", "Interesting and comfortable.", "Easy and exciting.", "Rough but very exciting."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2960, "question": "Hunters in Mississippi broke a state record for the heaviest alligator ever killed, kicking off the hunting season with two big catches. Dustin Bockman of Wisconsin and two hunting friends caught the 727-pound 13-foot-long beast on Sunday, beating last year's record-setter by 26 pounds, according to the state's Department of Wildlife, Fisheries and Parks. \"We're going to cook it for sure.\" he told Gulf Live. \"There's plenty for me and everybody else.\" He and his team of hunters followed the huge creature for 12 hours until they could get close enough to shoot him with a crossbow. \"He would go to the bottom and sit like a piece of wood. You could do anything with him,\" Bockman said. The hunters then had to figure out how to drag the beast's dead body into their boat. It look four hours of p...\n\nQ: According to the text, alligator hunting in Mississippi     _  .", "options": ["is a game for man", "often requires team work", "is allowed all year round", "has a history of SO years"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 858, "question": "In the decade of the 1970s, the United Nations organized several important meetings on the human environment to study a very serious problem.We humans are destroying the world around us.We must learn to protect them, or life will be very bad for our children and grandchildren. There are several major aspects to this problem. Population Most problems of the environment come from population growth.In 1700 there were 635 million people in the world; in 1900 there were 1.6 billion; in 1950, 2.5 billion; and in 1980, 4.4 billion.In the year 2010 there will be 7.3 billion.More people need more water, more food, more wood, and more petroleum. Distribution Scientists say there is enough water in the world for everyone, but some countries have a lot of water and some have only a little.Some areas g...\n\nQ: Good distribution means   _  .", "options": ["having things in the right place at the right time.", "cutting down forests and selling them to other countries.", "building water systems to carry water to farms.", "conserving our natural resources"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2255, "question": "Just getting accepted to an American college or university does not guarantee that you will get a visa. And getting a visa just lets you arrive in the United States. It does not guarantee that an immigration officer will permit you to enter the country. If you are requesting a visa for the first time, you will probably have to go to an American embassy or consulate . You will need to bring a government form sent to you by your American school that shows you have been accepted. You will also need banking and tax records that show you have enough money to pay for your education. And be prepared to provide evidence that you will return to your home country after your studies end. All of this is important in satisfying the requirements to get a visa. A consular official will also take your pic...\n\nQ: How much will you be charged for the visa application?", "options": ["Free of charge.", "Two hundred dollars.", "One hundred twenty dollars.", "Thirty dollars."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 429, "question": "Aqeela Asifi, who fled to Pakistan as a young woman, has spent her life teaching other Afghan refugees. For her efforts, Ms. Asifi, who is 49, has won the 2015 UNHCR Nansen Refugee Award. She also gets $100,000 to help pay for her education projects. The UNHCR Nansen Refugee Award honors extraordinary service to people who have been forced from their homes. Eleanor Roosevelt, Graca Machel and Luciano Pavarotti are some of the other winners of the award. Asifi faced many problems in Afghanistan before she fled to Pakistan. Resources were limited and education for women was discouraged. However, in Pakistan, the 49-year-old was able to bring change to her conservative Afghan community. She persuaded parents to send their daughters to school in a tent at the Kot Chandana refugee village. The ...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from the passage?", "options": ["Resources were unlimited and education for women was encouraged before Asifi fled to Pakistan.", "Eleanor Roosevelt, Graca Machel and Luciano Pavarotti all fled to other countries from Afghanistan.", "Asifi's daughters can enjoy equal opportunities like their brothers to receive higher education at university.", "Asifi still treats her own country with great affection though living as a refugee in another country."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 318, "question": "Cutting global warming pollution would not only make the planet healthier, it would make people healthier too, new research suggested. Cutting carbon dioxide emissions could save millions of lives, mostly by reducing preventable deaths from heart and lung diseases, according to studies released Wednesday and published in a special issue of The Lancet, a British medical journal. \"Relying on fossil fuels leads to unhealthy lifestyles, increasing our chances of getting sick and in some cases takes years from our lives,\" US Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius said in a telecast briefing from her home state of Kansas. \"As greenhouse gas emissions go down, so do deaths from cardiovascular and respiratory diseases. This is not a small effect.\" Instead of looking at the health il...\n\nQ: The new research differs from past studies in that   _  .", "options": ["it focuses on the immediate benefits of cutting carbon dioxide emissions", "it studies the bad effects arising from future global warming", "it is believed by more people", "it mainly targets at developing countries"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1102, "question": "\"Regardless of social class, race and age, men say they hate to shop.\" says Zukin, City University of New York sociology professor. Yet when you ask them deeper questions, it turns out that they like to shop. Men generally like to shop for books, music and hardware. But if you ask them about the shopping they do for books or music, they'll say, \"Well, that's not shopping. That's research.\" In other words, what men and women call \"buying things\" and how they approach that task are different. Women will wander through several 1,000-aquare-meter stores in search of the perfect party dress. Men will wander through 100 Internet sites in search of the perfect digital camcorder. Women see shopping as a social event. Men see it as a special task or a game to be won. \"Men are frequently shopping to...\n\nQ: Compared to women, men usually treat shopping more   _  .", "options": ["seriously", "honestly", "curiously", "foolishly"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 500, "question": "Every spring Beijing is choked by huge sandstorms.The sky turns a strange and frightening yellow colour as clouds of sand sweep down from the deserts of Mongolia and north-western China.Strong winds blow up the dust and cover everything in sight--in 2006,a storm dumped 330,000 tonnes of dust on Beijing in one night. The number of sandstorms has grown alarmingly over the years as the deserts have expanded.This is partly man-made and partly because of climate .Many grasslands have been overgrazed by sheep and goats,or ploughed up,leaving the soil dangerously exposed.Too much water has been taken out of rivers,and the situation is made worse by increasingly long-lasting droughts that have affected the northern half of China as the climate grows warmer and drier.The result is probably the wors...\n\nQ: In which section can this passage most likely be found in a newspaper?", "options": ["Science and technology.", "Weather.", "Environment.", "Health and life."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1774, "question": "Dear Santa Claus, My name is Amy. I am 9 years old. I have a problem at school. Can you help me, Santa? Kids laugh at me because of the way I walk and run and talk. I have cerebral palsy. I just want one day when no one laughs at me or makes fun of me. Love, Amy At radio station WJLT in Fort Wayne, Indiana, letters poured in for the Christmas Wish Contest. When Amy's letter arrived at the radio station, manager Lee Tobin read it carefully. He thought it would be good for the people in Fort Wayne to hear about this special third grader and her unusual wish. Mr. Tobin called up the local newspaper. The next day, a picture of Amy and her letter to Santa made the front page of the \"News Sentinel\". The story spread quickly. All across the country, newspapers and radio and television stations re...\n\nQ: Amy's letter showed that   _   .", "options": ["her school wasn't a good place for students like her", "her schoolmates cannot understand her disability", "she wanted to win Christmas Wish Contest", "she was often ignored in and out of class"], "answer": 1}]